<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gaming_Network</string>
    <string name="main_image">Main Image</string>
    <string name="our_games">Our Games</string>
    <string name="first">First</string>
    <string name="textview2">TextView2</string>
    <string name="textview4">TextView4</string>
    <string name="leaderboards">Leaderboards</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>

    <string-array name="Games">
        <item>BGMI</item>
        <item>Clash Royale</item>
        <item>Fortnite</item>
        <item>Call Of Duty Mobile</item>
        <item>FreeFire</item>
        <item>Valorant</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="about_us_para">If you were a "super awesome" Gamer, what medium would you choose to show people how good you are, at what you do?\n\nBy playing tournaments, of course.\n\nAt GamingNetwork We Dream of a better world where We can play video games all day long without having Our sanity questioned. We are an eSports gaming company based out of Bangalore, India. We conduct eSports or Competitive Gaming Tournaments that are played on Mobile. We currently have an Online eSports Portal. Our Online eSports Portal was launched in Aug 2020 with an idea of bringing the tournaments experience online &amp;amp; with a vision to reach out to every gamer in India. With a passion and a commitment to the best gaming experience, we at GamingNetwork, have strove to create a community for gamers.</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_para_1">We, GamingNetwork Entertainment Pvt Ltd, incorporated under the Companies Act, 2013 (hereinafter referred to as “Company” having its registered office A 102 Galaxy One Apts.\n\nKR Puram Banglore-560049, India, the creator of this Privacy Policy ensure our firm commitment to your privacy vis-à-vis the protection of your priceless information. In order to endow you with our uninterrupted use of services, we may collect and, in some circumstances, disclose information about you. To enhance better protection of your privacy we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.\n\nAll visitors to www.GamingNetwork.co.in (Website) are advised to read and understand our Privacy Policy carefully, as by accessing the Website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy and consent to the collection, storage and use of information relating to you as provided herein.\n\nIf you do not agree with the terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy, including in relation to the manner of collection or use of your information, please do not use or access the Site.\n\nIf you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you should contact our Customer Support Desk at support@GamingNetwork.co.in\n\nANY CAPITALIZED WORDS USED HENCEFORTH SHALL HAVE THE MEANING ACCORDED TO THEM UNDER THIS AGREEMENT. FURTHER, ALL HEADING USED HEREIN ARE ONLY FOR THE PURPOSE OF ARRANGING THE VARIOUS PROVISIONS OF THE AGREEMENT IN ANY MANNER. NEITHER THE USER NOR THE CREATERS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY MAY USE THE HEADING TO INTERPRET THE PROVISIONS CONTAINED WITHIN IT IN ANY MANNER.\n\n1. Definitions:\n\na. “We”, “Our”, and “Us” shall mean and refer to the creators of this privacy policy.\n\nb. “You”, “Your”, “Yourself” and “User” shall mean and refer to natural and legal individuals who use the Website.\n\nc. “Website” shall mean and refer to GamingNetwork created by the Company\n\nd. “Personal Information” shall mean and refer to any personally identifiable information that We may collect from You.\n\ne. “Third Parties” refer to any website, company or individual apart from the User and the creator of the Website.\n\n2. Overview\n\nWe commit to respecting your online privacy data. We further recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. Information that is considered personal about you by us includes, but is not limited to, your name, address, email address, phone number or other contact information\n\nIn order to access the tournaments or portal on this Website, you are required to provide the following information which includes, but is not limited to:\n\nName;\n\nEmail;n\nDOB;\n\nSocial media permissions;\n\nMobile number;\n\nGamertags;\n\nLocation; and\n\nany other permission or information required.\n\nThis privacy policy also applies to data we collect from users who are not registered as members of this site, including, but not limited to, browsing behavior, pages viewed etc.\n\n3. Notification of Modifications and Changes to the T&amp;C and Privacy Policy\n\nWe reserve the right to change the Terms and Privacy Policy from time to time as we deem fit, without any intimation to you, and your continued use of the site will signify your acceptance of any amendment to these terms.\n\nYou are therefore advised to re-read the Terms of Service on a regular basis. Should it be that you do not accept any of the modifications or amendments to the Terms, you may terminate your use of this Website immediately.\n\n4. Information We Collect\n\nOur Platform\'s online requisition form requires users to give us contact information (like your name, address, telephone number and email address), and demographic information (like your zip code/pin code). As a member, you are required to provide a valid email address at registration and choose a username or alias that represents your identity on our Website. This information is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the Site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the Site or not), your computer browser information, your IP address, and other information associated with your interaction with the Site.\n\nWe also collect and store personal information provided by you from time to time on the Site. We only collect and use such information from you that we consider necessary for achieving a seamless, efficient and safe experience, customized to your needs including:\n\n· To enable the provision of services opted for by you;\n\n· To communicate necessary account and product/service related information from time to time;\n\n· To allow you to receive quality customer care services;\n\n· To undertake necessary fraud and money laundering prevention checks, and comply with the highest security standards;\n\n· To comply with applicable laws, rules and regulations; and\n\n· To provide you with information and offers on products and services, on updates, on promotions, on related, affiliated or associated service providers and partners, that we believe would be of interest to you.\n\nWhere any service requested by you involves a third party, such information as is reasonably necessary by the Company to carry out your service request may be shared with such third party.\n\nWe also do use your contact information to send you offers based on your interests and prior activity. The Company may also use contact information internally to direct its efforts for product improvement, to contact you as a survey respondent, to notify you if you win any contest; and to send you promotional materials from its contest sponsors or advertisers.\n\nFurther, you may from time to time choose to provide payment related financial information (credit card, debit card, bank account details, billing address etc.) on the Site. We are committed to keeping all such sensitive data/information safe at all times and ensure that such data/information is only transacted over secure Site of approved payment gateways which are digitally encrypted, and provide the highest possible degree of care available under the technology presently in use.\n\nThe Company will not use your financial information for any purpose other than to complete a transaction with you.\n\nTo the extent possible, we provide you the option of not divulging any specific information that you wish for us not to collect, store or use. You may also choose not to use a particular service or feature on the Site, and opt out of any non-essential communications from the Company.\n\nFurther, transacting over the internet has inherent risks which can only be avoided by you following security practices yourself, such as not revealing account/login related information to any other person and informing our customer care team about any suspicious activity or where your account has/may have been compromised.\n\n5. How Information Is Collected\n\na. Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.\n\nb. We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.\n\nc. We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfilment of those purposes.\n\nd. We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.\n\ne. Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.\n\n6. Cookies\n\na. We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of our Websites. "Cookies" are small files sited on your hard drive that assist us in providing customized services. We also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". Cookies can also help us provide information, which is targeted to your interests. Cookies may be used to identify logged in or registered users.\n\nb. Third party vendors including www.google.com (“Google”) may use cookies to serve ads based on your visits to this Website. You may visit the Website of the third party and choose to opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising, if the third party offers such an option. You may choose to opt-out of the Double-click cookie that Google and its partners use for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings. (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor\'s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting aboutads.info.)\n\nc. The Website also has enabled the Google Analytics Advertising, which allows Google to collect data about users on our Website, in addition to Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers. You may choose to opt out of this by downloading and installing the Google Analytics opt-out add-on here https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.\n\n7. External Links on Website\n\nThe Website may include hyperlinks to other web sites or content or resources. We have no control over any Websites or resources, which are provided by companies or persons other than Us.\n\nYou acknowledge and agree that We are not responsible for the availability of any such external sites or resources, and does not endorse any advertising, products or other materials on or available from such Websites or resources.\n\nYou acknowledge and agree that We are not liable for any loss or damage which may be incurred by you as a result of the availability of those external sites or resources, or as a result of any reliance placed by you on the completeness, accuracy or existence of any advertising, products or other materials on, or available from, such Websites or resources. These third-party service providers and Third-Party Sites may have their own privacy policies governing the storage and retention of your personal information that you may be subject to. We recommend that when you enter a Third-Party Site, you review the Third Party Site’s privacy policy as it relates to safeguarding your personal information. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Website.\n\n8. Our Use of Your Information\n\nYour contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. Finally, we may use your IP address to help protect our partners and ourselves from fraud. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. We will transfer information about you if We are acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.\n\nWe may release your personal information to a third-party in order to comply with a Court Order or other similar legal procedure, or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law; prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss; or investigate or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or violations of Our Terms of Use. We may disclose personally identifiable information to parties in compliance with our Copyright Policy as mentioned in the Terms of Use as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. In such events, We may disclose name, address, country, phone number, email address and company name.\n\n9. Confidentiality\n\nYou further acknowledge that the Website may contain information which is designated confidential by Us and that you shall not disclose such information without our prior written consent.\n\nYour information is regarded as confidential and therefore will not be divulged to any third party, unless if legally required to do so to the appropriate authorities.\n\nWe will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your e-mail address for unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by us will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products.\n\n10. Our Disclosure of Your Information\n\nDue to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting and foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties. Under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or members may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our Website. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications would always remain private.\n\nAs a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed:\n\na. External Service Providers: There may be a number of services offered by external service providers that help you use our Websites. If you choose to use these optional services, and in the course of doing so, disclose information to the external service providers, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their private policy.\n\nb. Other Corporate Entities: We share much of our data, including personally identifiable information about you, with our parent and/or subsidiaries that are committed to serving your online needs and related services, throughout the world. Such data will be shared for the sole purpose of enhancing your browsing experience and providing our services to you. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protectively as they treat information they obtain from their other members. It is possible that We and/or its subsidiaries, or any combination of such, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that we would share some or all of your information in order to continue to provide the service. You will receive notice of such event (to the extent that it occurs).\n\nc. Law and Order: We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement and other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability.\n\n11. Accessing and Reviewing Information\n\nFollowing registration, you can review and change the information you submitted each time except your display name. If you change any information we may keep track of your old information. You can change your registration information such as: name, address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, and profile.\n\nWe will retain in our files information you have requested to remove for certain circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms and conditions. Further, such prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored \'back up\' systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.\n\n12. Control of Your Password\n\nWhen you sign up to become a Member, you will also be asked to choose a password. You are entirely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password. It is important that you protect it against unauthorized access of your account and information by choosing your password carefully, and keeping your password and computer secure by signing out after using our services.\n\nYou agree not to use the account, username, email address or password of another Member at any time or to disclose your password to any third party. If you choose to share this information with third parties to provide you additional services, you are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password and therefore should review each third party\'s privacy policy. You are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password, including fees. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. You agree to notify us immediately if you suspect any consistent unauthorized use of your account or access to your password even after changing it.\n\n13. Other Information Collectors\n\nExcept as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are on our Websites or on other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy policies. Since we do not control the privacy policies of the third parties, you are subject to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.\n\n14. Security\n\nWe treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by members inside and outside the company. We do not recommend transfer of sensitive information (such as credit card number) and bank account details via the Site to other Users. Users are recommended to do so offline, on the phone or via personal emails. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once We receive it. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. You therefore agree that any security breaches beyond the control of our standard security procedures are at your sole risk and discretion.\n\n15. Disclaimer\n\nWe cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information (including sensitive information like credit card information and bank account number) will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. Therefore, although we are committed to protecting your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information will always remain private. As a user of the Site, you understand and agree that you assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the Site, the internet generally, and the documents you post or access and for your conduct on and off the Site.\n\n16. Disputes and Jurisdiction\n\nAll disputes involving but not limited to rights conferred, compensation, refunds, and other claims through this policy will be resolved through a two-step Alternate Dispute Resolution mechanism.\n\na. Stage 1: Mediation. In case of a dispute, the matter will first be attempted to be resolved by a sole mediator who is a neutral third party and will be selected at the mutual acceptance of a proposed mediator by both parties. Both parties may raise a name for sole arbitrator and in case both parties accept the proposed name, the said person shall be appointed as sole mediator. In any case the parties are not able to reach a consensus within two proposed mediators, the Company reserves the right to decide who the final mediator is. The decision of the mediator is not binding on both parties, however the parties in good faith will attempt to bind by the decision.\n\nb. Stage 2: Arbitration. In case that mediation does not yield a result suitable or preferred by any one of the parties, arbitration may follow, the award of which is binding on both parties. The Arbitration Board shall comprise three members – one appointed by each party and the third member to be nominated by the two appointed members by mutual consent. Arbitration shall be held at Banglore, India. The proceedings of arbitration shall be in the English language. The arbitrator’s award shall be final and binding on the Parties. If the dispute cannot be resolved by this two-step Alternate Dispute Resolution mechanism, it shall be referred to the courts at Banglore, India.\n\n17. Questions and Suggestions\n\nIf you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you should contact us by sending an e-mail to support@GamingNetwork.co.in\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="terms_of_use_para">1. General\n\n

"www.gamingnetwork.co.in" (hereinafter, the “Website”) is owned and operated by GamingNetworkEntertainment Pvt Ltd (“Company”, “Gaming Network”), a company incorporated under the Companies Act, having its registered office at Bangalore

You are advised to read and understand these Terms carefully as moving past the home page, or using any of the services shall be taken to mean that You have read and agreed to all of the policies, which constitute a legally binding agreement between you and the Website. These terms are to be read along with the Privacy Policy and any other policies on the Website.

This document is an electronic record published in accordance with the provisions of the Information Technology (Intermediaries guidelines) Rules, 2011 that require publishing the Rules and Regulations, Privacy Policy and Terms of Service for access or usage of the Website and being generated by a computer system, it does not require any physical or digital signatures.

For the purpose of these Terms of Use, along with any amendments to the same, and wherever the context so requires “You”, “Your "or “User” refer to the person visiting, accessing, browsing through and/or using the Website at any point in time. The term “ We”, “Us”, “Our” shall mean and refer to the Website and/or the Company, depending on the context.

The headings of each section in this Agreement are only for the purpose of organizing the various provisions under this Agreement in an orderly manner. These headings shall not be used by either party to interpret the provisions contained under them in any manner. Further, the headings have no legal or contractual value.

We hold the sole right to modify the Terms of Service without prior permission from You or providing notice to You. The relationship creates on You a duty to periodically check the Terms of Service and stay updated on its requirements. If You continue to use the Website or avail any of its services without registration following such change, this is deemed as consent by You to the so amended policies. Your continued use of the Website is conditioned upon your compliance with the Terms of Service, including but not limited to compliance with the Terms of Service even after alterations, if any.

2. Services Overview

The Website is an online platform where Users can log on and subscribe to the portal. The subscription can be either monthly or yearly. Upon subscription the Users can gain access and intimation to various contests and tournaments across India. Winners of these tournaments shall be awarded with various prizes in the form of money and/or goodies.

3. Registration

To use the services provided on the Website and to access the portal, it is compulsory to create an account and subscribe. A User may create an account on the Website which shall collect only Your basic information. To create an account, you need to choose a username and password. You also have the option of linking your social media accounts, such as Your Face book or Google Plus account with the Gaming Network account, to create your Gaming Network Account. You must keep your account and registration details current and correct for communications related to your transactions on the Website.

At the time of registration, the Company shall collect the following personally identifiable information about you: Name - including first and last name, email address, mobile phone number, PAN Card and other contact details, demographic profile (like your age, gender, address, etc.,). If you choose to link your social media account with your Gaming Network Account, we collect basic information about you from those social media platforms, such as: name, age, gender, location and e-mail address. Information collected about you is subject to the Privacy Policy of the Company, which may be read as part and parcel of these Terms of Use.

You are solely responsible for protecting the confidentiality of your username and password and any activity under the account will be deemed to have been done by you. In the event you provide us with false/inaccurate details or the Company has a reasonable ground to believe that false and inaccurate information has been furnished, we hold the right to permanently suspend your account.

4. Eligibility

Services on the Website would be available to only select geographies in India. Persons who are “incompetent to contract” within the meaning of the Indian Contract Act, 1872 including minors, un-discharged insolvents etc. are not eligible to use the Website.

However, if you are a minor, i.e. under the age of 18 years and over the age of 13 years, you may use the Website under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by these Terms of Use. Gaming Network reserves the right to terminate or refuse your registration, or refuse to permit access to the Website, if it is discovered or brought to its notice that you are a minor.

5. Security

Transactions on the Website are secure and protected. Any information entered by the User when transacting on the Website is encrypted to protect the User against unintentional disclosure to third parties. The User’s credit and debit card information is not received, stored by or retained by the Company / Website in any manner. This information is supplied by the User directly to the relevant payment gateway which is authorized to handle the information provided, and is compliant with the regulations and requirements of various banks and institutions and payment franchisees that it is associated with.

6. License and Access

The Company grants you a limited sub-license to access and make personal use of the Website, but not to download (other than page caching) or modify it, or any portion of it, except with express written consent of the Company. Such limited sub- license does not include/permit any resale or commercial use of the Website or its contents; any collection and use of any listings, descriptions, or prices; any derivative use of the Website or its contents; any downloading or copying of information for the benefit of another merchant; or any use of data mining, robots, or similar data gathering and extraction tools. Any portion of the Website may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without express written consent of the Company. You may not frame or utilize framing techniques to enclose any trademark, logo, or other proprietary information (including images, text, page layout, or form) of the Website or of the Company and/or its affiliates without the express written consent of the Company. You may not use any meta tags or any other “hidden text” utilizing the Company’s name or trademarks without the express written consent of the Company. You shall not attempt to gain unauthorized access to any portion or feature of the Website, or any other systems or networks connected to the Website or to any server, computer, network, or to any of the services offered on or through the Website, by hacking, ‘password mining’ or any other illegitimate means.

You hereby agree and undertake not to host, display, upload, modify, publish, transmit, update or share any information which:

a. belongs to another person and to which you do not have any right;

b. is grossly harmful, harassing, blasphemous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, pedophilic, libelous, invasive of another’s privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically objectionable, disparaging, relating or encouraging money laundering or gambling, or otherwise unlawful in any manner whatever;

c. harms minors in any way;

d. infringes any patent, trademark, copyright or other proprietary/intellectual property rights;

e. violates any law for the time being in force;

f. deceives or misleads the addressee about the origin of such messages communicates any information which is grossly offensive or menacing in nature;

g. impersonates another person;

h. contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer resource;

i. threatens the unity, integrity, defense, security or sovereignty of India, friendly relations with foreign states, or public order or causes incitement to the commission of any cognizable offence or prevents investigation of any offence or is insulting any other nation; or

j. is misleading or known to be false in any way.

7. Communications

By using this Website, it is deemed that you have consented to receiving calls, autodialed and/or pre-recorded message calls, e-mails, from Us at any time with the use of the telephone number and e-mail address that has been provided by you for the use of this Website which are subject to the Privacy Policy. The user agrees to receive promotional communication and newsletters from the Company and its partners.

This includes contacting you through information received through other parties. The use of this Website is also your consent to receive SMS from Us at any time we deem fit. This consent to be contacted is for purposes that include and are not limited to clarification calls and marketing and promotional calls. The user can opt out from such communication and/or newsletters either by unsubscribing on the Website itself, or by contacting the customer services team and placing a request for unsubscribing by sending an email to support@GamingNetwork.co.in

You may also be contacted by Service Providers with whom we have entered into a contract in furtherance of our rights, duties and obligations under this document and all other policies followed by Us. Such contact will be made only in pursuance of such objectives, and no other calls will be made.

The sharing of the information provided by you will be governed by the Privacy Policy and We will not give out such contact information of yours to third parties not connected with the Website.

8. Payment

The following payment options are available on the Website:

(a) Domestic and international credit cards issued by banks and financial institutions that are part of the Visa, Master Card &amp; Amex Card networks;

(b) Visa &amp; Master Card Debit cards;

(c) Net banking/Direct Debit payments from select banks in India. A list of available options will be made available at the time of ‘checkout’.

(d) Third Party Payment gateways

9. User Obligations

You are a restricted user of this Website.

a. You are bound not to cut, copy, distribute, modify, recreate, reverse engineer, distribute, disseminate, post, publish or create derivative works from, transfer, or sell any information or software obtained from the Website. With our prior permission limited use may be allowed. For the removal of doubt, it is clarified that unlimited or wholesale reproduction, copying of the content for commercial or non-commercial purposes and unwarranted modification of data and information within the content of the Website is not permitted.

b. You agree not to access (or attempt to access) the Website and/or the materials or Services by any means other than through the interface that is provided by the Website. The use of deep-link, robot, spider or other automatic device, program, algorithm or methodology, or any similar or equivalent manual process, to access, acquire, copy or monitor any portion of the Website or Content, or in any way reproduce or circumvent the navigational structure or presentation of the Website, materials or any Content, to obtain or attempt to obtain any materials, documents or information through any means not specifically made available through the Website. You acknowledge and agree that by accessing or using the Website or Services, You may be exposed to content from other users that You may consider offensive, indecent or otherwise objectionable. We disclaim all liabilities arising in relation to such offensive content on the Website. Further, You may report such offensive content.

c. In places where this Website allows you to post or upload data/information, You undertake to ensure that such material is not offensive and in accordance with applicable laws. Further, You undertake not to:

i. Abuse, harass, threaten, defame, disillusion, erode, abrogate, demean or otherwise violate the legal rights of others;

ii. Engage in any activity that interferes with or disrupts access to the Website or the Services (or the servers and networks which are connected to the Website);

iii. Impersonate any person or entity, or falsely state or otherwise misrepresent Your affiliation with a person or entity;

iv. Publish, post, disseminate, any information which is grossly harmful, harassing, blasphemous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, pedophilic, libelous, invasive of another's privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically objectionable, disparaging, relating or encouraging money laundering or gambling, or otherwise unlawful in any manner whatever; or unlawfully threatening or unlawfully harassing including but not limited to "indecent representation of women" within the meaning of the Indecent Representation of Women (Prohibition) Act, 1986;

v. Post any file that infringes the copyright, patent or trademark of other legal entities;

vi. Upload or distribute files that contain viruses, corrupted files, or any other similar software or programs that may damage the operation of the Website or another's computer;

vii. Download any file posted by another user that you know, or reasonably should know, cannot be legally distributed in such manner;

viii. Probe, scan or test the vulnerability of the Website or any network connected to the Website, nor breach the security or authentication measures on the Website or any network connected to the Website. You may not reverse look-up, trace or seek to trace any information on any other user, of or visitor to, the Website, or any other customer of the Website, including any Website Account not owned by You, to its source, or exploit the Website or Service or information made available or offered by or through the Website, in any way whether or not the purpose is to reveal any information, including but not limited to personal identification information, other than Your own information, as provided for by the Website;

ix. Disrupt or interfere with the security of, or otherwise cause harm to, the Website, system resources, accounts, passwords, servers or networks connected to or accessible through the Website or any affiliated or linked Websites;

x. Collect or store data about other users in connection with the prohibited conduct and activities set forth in this Section;

xi. Use the Website or any material or Content for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms of Service, or to solicit the performance of any illegal activity or other activity which infringes the rights of this Website or other third parties;

xii. Violate any code of conduct or other guidelines, which may be applicable for or to any particular Service;

xiii. Violate any applicable laws or regulations for the time being in force within or outside India;

xiv. Violate the Terms of Service including but not limited to any applicable Additional Terms of the Website contained herein or elsewhere;

xv. Violate any code of conduct or other guidelines, which may be applicable for or to any particular Service;

xvi. Threaten the unity, integrity, defense, security or sovereignty of India, friendly relations with foreign states, or public order or cause incitement to the commission of any cognizable offence or prevent investigation of any offence or is insulting any other nation;

xvii. Publish, post, disseminate information that is false, inaccurate or misleading; violate any applicable laws or regulations for the time being in force in or outside India;

xviii. Directly or indirectly, offer, attempt to offer, trade or attempt to trade in any item, the dealing of which is prohibited or restricted in any manner under the provisions of any applicable law, rule, regulation or guideline for the time being in force;

xix. Create liability for Us or cause Us to lose (in whole or in part) the services of Our internet service provider ("ISPs") or other suppliers.

You shall not engage in advertising to, or in solicitation of, other Users of the Website to buy or sell any products or services, including, but not limited to, products or services related to that being displayed on the Website or related to us. You may not transmit any chain letters or unsolicited commercial or junk email to other Users via the Website. It shall be a violation of these Terms of Service to use any information obtained from the Website in order to harass, abuse, or harm another person, or in order to contact, advertise to, solicit, or sell to another person other than Us without Our prior explicit consent. We can (and You hereby expressly authorize Us to) disclose any information about You to law enforcement or other government officials, as we, in our sole discretion, believe it necessary or appropriate in connection with the investigation and/or resolution of possible crimes, especially those that may involve personal injury. In order to protect Our Users from such advertising or solicitation, We reserve the right to restrict the number of messages or emails which a user may send to other Users in any 24-hour period which We deem appropriate in our sole discretion. You understand that We have the right at all times to disclose any information (including the identity of the persons providing information or materials on the Website) as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation or valid governmental request. This may include, without limitation, disclosure of the information in connection with investigation of alleged illegal activity or solicitation of illegal activity or in response to a lawful court order or subpoena.

We have no obligation to monitor the materials posted on the Website. We shall have the right to remove or edit any content that in its sole discretion violates, or is alleged to violate, any applicable law or either the spirit or letter of these Terms of Service.In no event shall We assume or have any responsibility or liability for any Content posted or for any claims, damages or losses resulting from the use of Content and/or appearance of Content on the Website. You hereby represent and warrant that You have all necessary rights in and to all Content which You provide and all information it contains and that such Content shall not infringe any proprietary or other rights of third parties or contain any libelous, tortuous, or otherwise unlawful information.

10. Copyright and Trademark

The Company, its suppliers and licensors expressly reserve all intellectual property rights in all text, programs, services, processes, technology, images, content and other materials which appear on the Website. Access to or use of the Website does not confer and should not be considered as conferring upon anyone any license to the Company or any third party’s intellectual property rights. All rights, including copyright, in and to the Website are owned by or licensed to the Company. Any use of the Website or its contents, including copying or storing it or them in whole or part is prohibited without the permission of the Company.

You may not modify, distribute or re-post anything on the Website for any purpose. The names and logos and all related product and service names, design marks and slogans are the trademarks/service marks of the Company, its affiliates, its partners or its suppliers/service providers. All other marks are the property of their respective owners. No trademark or service mark license is granted in connection with the materials contained on the Website. Access to or use of the Website does not authorize anyone to use any name, logo or mark in any manner. References on the Website to any names, marks, products or services of third parties or hypertext links to third party Websites or information are provided solely as a convenience to you and do not in any way constitute or imply the Company’s endorsement, sponsorship or recommendation of the third party, the information, its services.

The Company is not responsible for the content of any third party Websites and does not make any representations regarding the content or accuracy of material on such Websites. If you decide to access a link of any third party Websites, you do so entirely at your own risk and expense.

11. Disclaimer of Warranties and Liabilities

YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT, TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW:

THE Website, SERVICES AND OTHER MATERIALS ARE PROVIDED BY THIS Website IS ON AN "AS IS" BASIS WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS, IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, GamingNetwork MAKES NO WARRANTY THAT

a. YOUR REQUIREMENTS WILL BE MET OR THAT SERVICES PROVIDED WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE OR ERROR-FREE;

b. MATERIALS, INFORMATION AND RESULTS OBTAINED WILL BE EFFECTIVE, ACCURATE OR RELIABLE;

c. ANY ERRORS OR DEFECTS IN THE Website, SERVICES OR OTHER MATERIALS WILL BE CORRECTED.

TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, WE WILL HAVE NO LIABILITY RELATED TO USER CONTENT ARISING UNDER INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS, LIBEL, PRIVACY, PUBLICITY, OBSCENITY OR OTHER LAWS. Gaming Network ALSO DISCLAIMS ALL LIABILITY WITH RESPECT TO THE MISUSE, LOSS, MODIFICATION OR UNAVAILABILITY OF ANY USER CONTENT.

THE USER UNDERSTANDS AND AGREES THAT ANY MATERIAL OR DATA DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE Website IS DONE ENTIRELY AT HIS/HER OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND HE/SHE WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO HIS/HER COMPUTER SYSTEMS OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF SUCH MATERIAL OR DATA. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY TYPOGRAPHICAL ERROR LEADING TO AN INVALID COUPON. Gaming Network ACCEPTS NO LIABILITY FOR ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS, WITH RESPECT TO ANY INFORMATION PROVIDED TO YOU WHETHER ON BEHALF OF ITSELF OR THIRD PARTIES.

WE SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY THIRD PARTY PRODUCT OR SERVICES. THE ADVERTISEMENT AVAILABLE ON E-MAIL OR Website WITH RESPECT TO THE THIRD PARTY Website OR THE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES ARE FOR INFORMATION PURPOSE ONLY.

12. Indemnification and Limitation of Liability

YOU AGREE TO INDEMNIFY, DEFEND AND HOLD HARMLESS THIS Website/COMPANY INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ITS AFFILIATE VENDORS, AGENTS AND EMPLOYEES FROM AND AGAINST ANY AND ALL LOSSES, LIABILITIES, CLAIMS, DAMAGES, DEMANDS, COSTS AND EXPENSES (INCLUDING LEGAL FEES AND DISBURSEMENTS IN CONNECTION THEREWITH AND INTEREST CHARGEABLE THEREON) ASSERTED AGAINST OR INCURRED BY US THAT ARISE OUT OF, RESULT FROM, OR MAY BE PAYABLE BY VIRTUE OF, ANY BREACH OR NON-PERFORMANCE OF ANY REPRESENTATION, WARRANTY, COVENANT OR AGREEMENT MADE OR OBLIGATION TO BE PERFORMED BY YOU PURSUANT TO THESE TERMS OF SERVICE. FURTHER, YOU AGREE TO HOLD US HARMLESS AGAINST ANY CLAIMS MADE BY ANY THIRD PARTY DUE TO, OR ARISING OUT OF, OR IN CONNECTION WITH, YOUR USE OF THE Website, ANY CLAIM THAT YOUR MATERIAL CAUSED DAMAGE TO A THIRD PARTY, YOUR VIOLATION OF THE TERMS OF SERVICE, OR YOUR VIOLATION OF ANY RIGHTS OF ANOTHER, INCLUDING ANY INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS.

IN NO EVENT SHALL Gaming Network, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, PARTNERS OR SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE TO YOU, THE VENDOR OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING THOSE RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WHETHER OR NOT FORESEEABLE OR WHETHER OR NOT WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, OR BASED ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, INCLUDING BREACH OF CONTRACT OR WARRANTY, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION, OR ANY OTHER CLAIM ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF OR ACCESS TO THE Website, SERVICES OR MATERIALS.

THE LIMITATIONS AND EXCLUSIONS IN THIS SECTION APPLY TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW.

13. Termination

This User Agreement is effective unless and until terminated by either you or the Company. You may terminate this User Agreement at any time, provided that you discontinue any further use of the Website. The Company may terminate this User Agreement at any time and may do so immediately without notice, and accordingly deny you access to the Website.

Such termination will be without any liability to the Company. The Company’s right to any Comments and to be indemnified pursuant to the terms hereof, shall survive any termination of this User Agreement. Any such termination of the User Agreement shall not cancel your obligation to pay for product(s) already ordered from the Website or affect any liability that may have arisen under the User Agreement prior to the date of termination.

14. Hosting of Third Party Information

The Website hosts information provided by third parties. We are in no manner responsible to you for the accuracy, legitimacy and trueness of the information so hosted. We take reasonable care to ensure such accuracy but we are not responsible for the information so furnished. You agree to not hold us liable for the falsification of any such provided information.

15. Disputes and Jurisdiction

All disputes involving but not limited to rights conferred, compensation, refunds, and other claims will be resolved through a two-step Alternate Dispute Resolution mechanism.

a. Stage 1: Mediation. In case of a dispute, the matter will first be attempted to be resolved by a sole mediator who is a neutral third party and will be selected at the mutual acceptance of a proposed mediator by both parties. Both parties may raise a name for the sole mediator and in the case both parties accept the proposed name, the said person shall be appointed as sole mediator. In case the parties are not able to reach a consensus within two proposed mediators, the Company reserves the right to decide who the final mediator is. The decision of the mediator is not binding on both parties.

b. Stage 2: Arbitration. In case that mediation does not yield a result suitable or preferred by any one of the parties, arbitration may follow, the award of which is binding on both parties. The Arbitration Board shall comprise three members – one appointed by each party and the third member to be nominated by the two appointed members by mutual consent. Arbitration shall be held at Banglore, India. The proceedings of arbitration shall be in the English language. The arbitrator’s award shall be final and binding on the Parties.

If the dispute cannot be resolved by this two-step Alternate Dispute Resolution mechanism, it shall be referred to the courts at Banglore.

16. Privacy

We encourage you to read the Privacy Policy and to use the information it contains to make informed decisions regarding Your personal information. Please also note that certain information, statements, data and content (such as but not limited to photographs) which You provide on the Website are likely to reveal Your gender, ethnic origin, nationality, age, and/or other personal information about You. You acknowledge and agree that your submission of such information is voluntary on Your part. Further, You acknowledge, consent and agree that we may access, preserve, and disclose information You provide to Us at any stage during Your use of the Website. Disclosures of information to Third Parties are further addressed in Our Privacy Policy.

17. Miscellaneous Provisions

a. Entire Agreement: The terms and conditions set forth in this Section 3 and any additional or different terms expressly agreed by Client and Service vendor shall constitute the entire agreement and understanding of Client and Service vendor with respect to each Service Contract and shall cancel and supersede any other prior or contemporaneous discussions, agreements, representations, warranties, and/or other communications between them. Notwithstanding the foregoing, the Client and Service vendor shall always remain subject to the terms of the user Agreement.

b. Waiver: The failure of either party at any time to require performance of any provision of this Agreement in no manner shall affect such party's right at a later time to enforce the same. No waiver by either party of any breach of this Agreement, whether by conduct or otherwise, in any one or more instances, shall be deemed to be, or construed as, a further or continuing waiver of any other such breach, or a waiver of any other breach of this Agreement.

c. Severability: If any provision of this Agreement shall to any extent be held invalid, illegal or unenforceable, the validity, legality and enforceability of the remaining provisions of this Agreement shall in no way be affected or impaired thereby and each such provision of this Agreement shall be valid and enforceable to the fullest extent permitted by law. In such a case, this Agreement shall be reformed to the minimum extent necessary to correct any invalidity, illegality or unenforceability, while preserving to the maximum extent the rights and commercial expectations of the parties hereto, as expressed herein.

18. EA SPORTS

This tournament [and/or tournament web site] is not affiliated with the EA SPORTS FIFA 18 Global Series or sponsored by Electronic Arts Inc. or its licensor(s).

19. Age Requirements

You must be at least 18 years old to join our Gaming community.

20. Data security:

We store our user data in a secure database which also includes users email address and passwords

Data security includes data encryption, hashing, tokenization, and key management practices that protect data across all our applications and platforms.

21.Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you should contact us by sending an e-mail to support@GamingNetwork.co.in

22.Refund policy

If the tournamnet you have joined for any reason, the amount paid will be automatically refunded to the gaming network wallet, which can be withdrawn. For any concerns, contact us by sending an e-mail to support@GamingNetwork.co.in</string>

    <string name="faq_para_1">1. How do I Sign Up on the Gaming Network Website?</string>

    <string name="faq_para_1_ans">Go to gamingnetwork.co.in/signup\n\nGive your details and verify the OTP received on your mobile.\n\nAnd whoop you’ve signed up. Enjoy your gaming experience.</string>
</resources>